&gt;&gt; Hi Bryan.
&gt;&gt; こんにちは ブライアン
&gt;&gt; Hey David.
&gt;&gt; やあ デビッド
&gt;&gt; So, you've got a pretty impressive title,
&gt;&gt; あなたの肩書はかなり印象的ですね
Vice President of Applied Deep Learning Research.
応用ディープラーニング調査担当副社長ですよね
What does a vice president do all day?
副社長は1日中何をしているのですか?
&gt;&gt; That's a great question, actually.
&gt;&gt; 実にいい質問です
Right now, I'm looking for people with deep learning experience to come join my team.
現在 チームに加わってもらおうと ディープラーニングの経験者を探しています
But, most of my career,
私はキャリアの大半を
I've spent building deep neural networks,
深層ニューラルネットワークとディープラーニング用インフラストラクチャーの構築に
and infrastructure for deep learning,
費やしてきました
and I still spend a lot of my time on that.
今でも多くの時間をかけています
&gt;&gt; All right. So, impress me.
&gt;&gt; なるほど感心しますね
What's the most amazing thing you've ever done with deep neural networks?
深層ニューラルネットワークを使ってみて 今までで最も素晴らしかったことは何ですか?
&gt;&gt; Well, one of the things I'm most proud of is that,
&gt;&gt; 私が最も誇りに思っていることの1つは
I wrote a library that became cuDNN,
cuDNNになったライブラリーを作成したことです
which has become really important for using
GPUを使って深層ニューラルネットワークのトレーニングを加速するためには
GPUs to accelerate deep neural network training.
これが非常に重要です
&gt;&gt; All right. I'm impressed.
&gt;&gt; わかりました印象深いです
Bryan's being a little modest.
ブライアンは控えめに言っていますが
cuDNN has become so important, in fact,
実際 cuDNNは非常に重要になってきており
that it's effectively a requirement for successfully training deep neural networks.
事実上 深層ニューラルネットワークを正しくトレーニングするための要件です
&gt;&gt; Well, I certainly think so.
&gt;&gt; 確かにそう思います
&gt;&gt; So, cuDNN is great.
&gt;&gt; だからcuDNNは素晴らしいです
I would be happy if I built one project too successful as cuDNN in my life.
もし自分なら 人生のなかで1つのプロジェクトをcuDNNとして構築できたら大変光栄です
But beyond cuDNN, what's
cuDNN以外に
the most exciting deep neural network you've been working on recently?
最近取り組んでいる 最もエキサイティングな深層ニューラルネットワークは何ですか?
&gt;&gt; Well, the last big project I did was at Baidu,
&gt;&gt; 私が最後に携わった大きなプロジェクトはBaiduでした
and I was part of the deep speech team,
私は深層スピーチチームの一員であり
where we built a new kind of end-to-end deep neural
そこで英語と中国語の音声認識のための
network for speech recognition in English, and Mandarin Chinese.
新しい種類のエンドツーエンド深層ニューラルネットワークを構築しました
&gt;&gt; That is amazing.
&gt;&gt; すごいですね